Guide to the Albert C. Woodroof and A. C. Woodroof, Jr. Papers and Architectural Drawings
Albert C. Woodroof and A. C. Woodroof, Jr. Papers and Architectural Drawings
- Drawings, 1927-1977; 1927 1977
  - Albert C. Woodroof Drawings, 1929-1986; 1929 1986
    - North Carolina Agriculture and Technical College (2 of 2), 1948; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; McKinn & Norfleet (Tube 220)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; McKinn & Norfleet; Greensboro (N.C.)
    - North Carolina National Guard Armory Unit: Revisions, 1936 (Tube 143)
      Flag pole setting, entrance motif, boiler room, floor plans, elevations, heating
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Madison (N.C.)
    - Northwood Terrace Courts for the Northwood Housing Corporation, 1942 (Tube 133)
      Type "A" building, type "B" building
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Durham (N.C.)
    - Northwood Terrace Courts for the Northwood Housing Corporation, 1942 (Tube 143)
      Type "B" building
    - Oakview School Building: Cafeteria and kitchen, 1944 (Tube 158)
    - Our Father Lutheran Church, 1929 (Flatfolder 7)
    - Our Father Lutheran Church (1 of 2), 1962 (Tube 155)
    - Our Father Lutheran Church (2 of 2), 1962 (Tube 171)
    - Our Father Lutheran Church, 1962 (Tube 142)
    - Park Street School Building: Alterations and Additions, 1948 (Tube 116)
    - Parks and Recreation Commission: City of Greensboro, 1966 (Tube 189)
    - Patterson (Mr. & Mrs. F. A.) residence, 1951 (Tube 119)
      Alterations and additions, floor plans, elevations
    - Peace United Church of Christ: Sign, 1963; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 238)
    - Penn, Incorporated - Rockingham Company: Plat of survey for the city of Reidsville, 1969 (Flatfolder 17)
    - Pine Needles Inn: Golf Club building addition, 1942 (Tube 143)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Southern Pines (N.C.)
    - Pitt Technical Institute, 1968 (Tube 93)
      Additions, details
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Dudley & Shoe Architects; Greenville (N.C.)
    - Pitt Technical Institute: Classroom building, 1967 (Tube 100)
      Dudley & Shoe Architects; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Pitt County (N.C.)
    - Pitt Technical Institute: New classroom and laboratory building, 1968 (Tube 150)
      Dudley & Shoe Architects; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Greenville (N.C.)
    - Pitt Technical Institute: New classroom and laboratory building, 1968 (Tube 151)
    - Pomona Manufcaturing Co.: Store building alterations (Tube 165)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Pomona (N.C.)
    - Presbyterian Church of the Covenant: Alteration and addition, 1963; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 211)
    - Presnell (Dr. O. L.) residence, 1938 (Tube 119)
    - Proposed Addition to a Residence for the College President, 1966 (Tube 148)
    - Proposed Addition to a Residence for the College President, 1966 (Tube 92)
    - Proposed Addition to a Residence for the College President, 1966-1967 (Tube 100)
    - Proposed Addition to a Residence for the College President, 1966-1967 (Tube 101)
    - Proposed theatre (Tube 166)
    - Proposed warehouse building, 1944 (Tube 143)
      Floor plans, elevations, transverse sections
    - Proximity Manufactoring Co.: Office building alterations, 1945 (Tube 143)
      Partition details, floor plans, elevations
    - Proximity Manufacturing Co.: Conversion of the substation building into an office building, 1945 (Tube 143)
    - Randleman School Building: Addition, 1938 (Tube 159)
    - Randolph County Courthouse (Tube 166)
      Courtoom perspective
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Randolph (N.C.)
    - Randolph Oil Co., 1938 (Tube 166)
    - Religious Society of Friends: Meeting House (1 of 2), 1956; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 229)
    - Religious Society of Friends: Meeting House (2 of 2), 1956; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 230)
    - Remington Rand. Inc.: Office alterations, 1943 (Tube 133)
    - Residence on Kirby Drive: Starmount (1 of 2), 1947 (Tube 85)
    - Residence on Kirby Drive: Starmount (2 of 2), 1947 (Tube 119)
    - Revolution Cotton Mills: Alterations and additions to the office building, 1945 (Tube 103)
    - Revolution Cotton Mills: Dry Store Building alteration, 1946 (Tube 143)
    - Revolution Cotton Mills: Quill storage room alterations and addition, 1946 (Tube 143)
    - Rockingham County Extension Building, 1939 (Tube 167)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Reidsville (N.C.)
    - Rockingham County Extension Building: addition, 1939 (Tube 166)
    - Rockingham County Home Dormitory building for negroes, 1935 (Tube 166)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Rockingham County (N.C.)
    - Rockingham County Jail: Addition, 1939 (Tube 166)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Wentworth (N.C.)
    - Sanier-William Co., Inc.: Addition to Plant, 1967 (Tube 99)
    - Security National Bank: Parking lot shelter, 1956 (Tube 103)
    - Sedgefield Country Club (1 of 2), 1954; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 231)
    - Sedgefield Country Club (2 of 2), 1954; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 232)
    - Sedgefield Inn Co.: Additions (Tube 133)
      Floor plans, wall sections, elevations, reflected ceiling plan
    - Sellars (Mr. W. B.) residence, 1940 (Tube 119)
    - Smith (Sidney) residence, 1935 (Tube 139)
      Construction plans, plot plan, floor plan, elevations
    - Snow (Mr. John Edward, Jr.) residence, 1972 (Tube 153)
      Floor plans, foundation, elevation, sections
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; North Myrtle Beach (S.C.)
    - Snyder Memorial Baptist Church (1 of 2), 1958-1959; Woodroof A. C. (Albert Cecil) Jr. 1920-1991; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 197)
      Woodroof A. C. (Albert Cecil) Jr. 1920-1991; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Fayetteville (N.C.)
    - Snyder Memorial Baptist Church (2 of 2), 1958-1959; Woodroof A. C. (Albert Cecil) Jr. 1920-1991; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 198)
    - Sout (Mr. & Mrs. Ferd R.) residence, 1940 (Tube 149)
      Designs for bath and lavatory
    - Spence (Mr. J. A.) offices: Alterations and additions, 1939 (Tube 166)
    - Stern (Mrs. A.) residence, 1934 (Tube 138)
      Floor plans, construction details, sections, elevations
    - Stokesdale School: Addition, 1937 (Tube 158)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Stokesdale (N.C.)
    - Stout (Mr. Ferd R.) residence, 1940 (Tube 145)
    - Straughan (Miss Alice) garage building alterations (Tube 165)
    - Straughan (Miss Alice) residence, 1938 (Tube 154)
      Details, plot plan, floor plans, elevations
    - Straughn's Book Shop: Fixtures, 1943 (Tube 165)
    - Summerfield Negro School: Addition, 1950; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986 (Tube 208)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Summerfield (N.C.)
    - Sumner Township Public School: Home Economics Building, 1939 (Tube 158)
    - Tennis Pavilion, 1962 (Flatfolder 4)
    - Tennis Pavilion, 1962 (Flatfolder 2)
    - Tennis Pavilion (Flatfolder 3)
      A.E. Finley Foundation; Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Greensboro (N.C.)
    - Thayer (Mr. Cleveland) residence, 1936 (Tube 138)
      Floor plan, elevations
    - Trinity Methodist Church, 1956 (Tube 159)
    - Union Grove Methodist Church, 1946 (Tube 124)
      Floor plans, wall sections, elevations
    - United Securities Company: Office alterations, 1959 (Tube 155)
    - United Securities Company: Office alterations, 1959 (Tube 163)
      Heating and air conditioning floor plans
    - United Service Organizations: Building annex, 1943 (Tube 144)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; New York (N.Y.)
    - United Service Organizations (N.C.C.S.): Building 101-3 Pointdexter St. alterations (1 of 2), 1943 (Tube 144)
      Woodroof Albert C. 1895-1986; Elizabeth City (N.C.)
    - United Service Organizations (N.C.C.S.): Building 101-3 Pointdexter St. alterations (2 of 2), 1943 (Tube 165)
    - United Service Organizations: Information Center, 1945 (Tube 144)
      Attic exhaust fan installation, U.S. Entrance doors, floor plans
    - Vassar (Mr. And Mrs. Walter E.) residence, 1940 (Tube 110)
    - Virginia Ragsdale House: Proposed addition, 1965 (Tube 148)
    - Virginia Ragsdale House: Proposed addition for Dr. & Mrs. Grimsley Hobbs, 1965 (Tube 100)
    - Wall (Mr. & Mrs. J. E.) residence, 1974 (Tube 153)
      Foundation, electric plan, floor plan, sections, elevations
    - Weaver (Mr. Raymond W.) residence, 1936 (Tube 153)
      Floor plans, elevations, sections, details
    - West (Mr. Harvey A.) residence, 1937 (Tube 138)
      Garage apartment, floor plan, sections, elevations
    - Westridge School: Cabinets & Cork Boards for Classroom #9-#12, 1959 (Tube 162)
    - Wilking (Mr. J. D.) residence, 1935 (Tube 149)
    - Wingler (Mr. Harvey A.) residence, 1957 (Tube 149)
    - Woodroof (A.C) residence renovations, 1986 (Flatfolder 17)
    - Woodroof (Albert) office, 1954 (Flatfolder 17)
    - Woodroof (Mrs. Albert C.) corner cupboard, 1977 (Tube 153)
    - Yates (Mr. F. O.) residence, 1937 (Tube 141)
    - Yates (Mr. F. O.) residence, 1951 (Tube 119)
      Sections, floor plans, details, elevations
    - York (Wm. M.) residence, 1967 (Tube 153)
- Project Files, 1956-1974; 1956 1974
  Project files contain correspondence, financial records, contracts and agreements, and other material relating primarily to Woodroof, Jr.’s firm.
  - ABC Retail Store (1 of 3), 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - ABC Retail Store (2 of 3), 1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - ABC Retail Store (3 of 3), 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ABC Retail Store: Certificates, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Banks (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Barker-Cochran Construction Company: Proposed office building, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Beard Buildings, Inc., 1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Beard Buildings, Inc.: Office building specifications, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Beard Office Building, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Beard Office Building: Owner's file, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bessemer Junior High School (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Bessemer Junior High School (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Bessemer Junior High School, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Bessemer Junior High School, Clyde A. Erwin Elementary School, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bessemer Junior High School, Clyde A. Erwin Elementary School, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Bessemer Junior High School: Demolition of obsolete facilities, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Bessemer Street School: Talley Electric Company, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Best (Dr. James E.) office building, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Black Cadillac-Oldsmobile: Proposed new building (1 of 2), 1965 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Black Cadillac-Oldsmobile: Proposed new building (2 of 2), 1965 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Brooks-Anton Apartments, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Brown Realty Company, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Cameron-Brown Company: Office building, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - City Motors, Inc.: City rambler, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - City of High Point, North Carolina, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    High Point (N.C.)
  - Clyde A. Erwin Elementary School: Addition, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Clyde A. Erwin Elementary School: Certificates, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Clyde A. Erwin Elementary School: Correspondence (1 of 2), 1966-1969 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Clyde A. Erwin Elementary School: Correspondence (2 of 2), 1966-1969 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Clyde A. Erwin Elementary School: Dick and Kirkman, Inc., 1968 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Clyde A. Erwin Elementary School: Dixon and Waynick, Inc. certificates, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Clyde A. Erwin Elementary School: Talley Electric Company certificates, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Clyde A. Erwin Elementary School: Transmittal forms, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Construction Specification Institute, 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Elks Club, 1965-1970 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Elks Club: Certificates and Change Orders (1 of 2), 1966 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Elks Club: Certificates and change orders (2 of 2), 1966 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Elks Club: Planning file, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Elks Club: Sauna, 1967-1969 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Falk (Mr. and Mrs. Herbert, Jr.) residence, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Falk (Mr. and Mrs. Herbert, Jr.) residence, correspondence, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Correspondence (1 of 3), 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Correspondence (2 of 3), 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Correspondence (3 of 3), 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Rehabilitation Center (1 of 4), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Rehabilitation Center (2 of 4), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Rehabilitation Center (3 of 4), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Rehabilitation Center (4 of 4), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Rehabilitation Center, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Rehabilitation Center, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Fellowship Hall, Inc.: Rehabilitation Center, grading and site drainage, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - First Baptist Church: Proposed sanctuary, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    North Wilkesboro (N.C.)
  - First Baptist Church: Sound amplification system, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - First National Bank of Reidsville: Pennrose Branch, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - First Presbyterian Church, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - First Presbyterian Church Apartment Building: Certificates, change orders, statements, 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - First Presbyterian Church Apartment Building: Talley Electric Company, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - First Presbyterian Church: Cemetery wall, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - First Presbyterian Church: Coat racks, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - First Presbyterian Church: Memorial Building, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - First Presbyterian Church: Organ project, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - First Presbyterian Church: Property committee, 1961-1971 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - First Southern Building: Color Schedule, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - First Southern Building: Correspondence (1 of 2), 1960-1962 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - First Southern Building: Correspondence (2 of 2), 1960-1962 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - First Southern Building: General construction, 1960-1963 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - First Southern Building: Letters of transmittal, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - First Southern Building: Temperature and relative humidity tests, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Grandfather Mountain, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Greensboro Country Club: Minutes, reports, correspondence (1 of 2), 1960-1962 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Greensboro Country Club: Minutes, reports, correspondence (2 of 2), 1960-1962 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Greensboro Country Club: Pool, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Greensboro Country Club: Tennis pavilion, correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Greensboro Junior Museum: Addition number 3 specifications, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Greensboro Junior Museum: Alterations and unit number 3 addition, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Greensboro Junior Museum: Alterations and unit number 3 addition, requests for payments and change orders, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Greensboro Junior Museum: Board of Directors, 1958-1962 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Greensboro Junior Museum: Change orders and certificates, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Greensboro Junior Museum: Display cases, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Greensboro Junior Museum: General file, 1956-1958 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Greensboro Junior Museum: Hardware, drawings, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Greensboro Junior Museum: Planetarium (1 of 2), 1960 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Greensboro Junior Museum: Planetarium (2 of 2), 1961 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Greensboro Junior Museum: Report on Examination, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Greensboro Junior Museum: Unit number 3, preliminary bids and addendum, 1962-1963 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Greensboro Parks and Recreation Commission: Tennis pavilion, specifications (1 of 2), 1963 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Greensboro Parks and Recreation Commission: Tennis pavilion, specifications (2 of 2), 1962 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Guilford County Mental Retardation Unit (1 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Guilford County (N.C.)
  - Guilford County Mental Retardation Unit (2 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - King's Arms Apartments (1 of 2), 1964-1966 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - King's Arms Apartments (2 of 2), 1964-1966 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - King's Arms Apartments: Data, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Lambeth-Troxler Funeral Service, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Leaksville Publishing Company (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Leaksville Publishing Company (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Leaksville Publishing Company: Certificates, change orders, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Eden (N.C.)
  - Leaksville Publishing Company: Correspondence, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Leaksville Publishing Company: Transmittal forms, bidding documents, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Lemans Apartment, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Burlington (N.C.)
  - Lutheran Church of Our Father: Correspondence, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Lutheran Church of Our Father: Parish house, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Lutheran Church of Our Father: Parish house, contracts, payments, 1962-1963 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Lutheran Church of Our Father: Parish house, specifications, bids, 1962-1963 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - M&M Mall Shopping Center, 1969-1972 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - M&M Mall Shopping Center: Southern National Bank (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - M&M Mall Shopping Center: Specifications, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - M&M Mall Shopping Center: Winn-Dixie, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - McCall-Boykin Truck, Inc., 1965 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Baltimore (Md.)
  - McLendon, Brim, Brooks, Pierce and Daniels: Office renovations, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous papers (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Specifications (1 of 5) (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Specifications (2 of 5) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Specifications (3 of 5) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Specifications (4 of 5) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Specifications (5 of 5) (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Moore Realty Company (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Morris (Mr. Lewis) residence, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Motsinger Apartments, 1966-1968 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Graham (N.C.)
  - National Olympic Clubs: Preliminary correspondence, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Norman (George E.) residence, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - North Carolina Medical Care Commission: Prospective nursing home, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - North State Telephone Company, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - O. Henry Townhouses, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Opportunity Center, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Wentworth (N.C.)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Addendum number 3, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Bid, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Bidding documents, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Bowes Construction Company, certificates, change orders, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Contracts and correspondence (1 of 2), 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Contracts and correspondence (2 of 2), 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Davidson and Jones, Inc., certificates, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Davidson and Jones, Inc., correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Eckerd Drug Stores, correspondence, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Endicott Johnson, correspondence, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Field supervision reports, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Frank Penn correspondence, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: General Sprinkler Corporation, correspondence, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Grading and site drainage, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Hardee's Food Systems, Inc., correspondence, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Mechanical contracts, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Miscellaneous correspondence, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Mr. Van Weatherspoon correspondence, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Myatt and Associates, correspondence, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Owner-architect agreement, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Owner-contractor agreement, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Phase A, 1968-1972 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Phase B, 1968-1970 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Phase B, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Phase B, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Rose's Stores, Inc., correspondence, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Soil compaction inspection, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Specifications, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Sutton and Kennerly, correspondence, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Toilet partitions, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Pennrose Mall Shopping Center: Winn-Dixie, Inc., correspondence, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Post Office addition, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    Mebane (N.C.)
  - Presbyterian House, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Presbyterian House, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Presbyterian House, 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Presbyterian House: Bids and contracts, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Presbyterian House: Requests for payments, change orders, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Richardson Realty Company: Preliminary correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Ridgeway Enterprises, Inc.: Commerce park, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - S. A. Peeler Elementary School, 1967-1970 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Schenck, Mr. and Mrs. J. S., III: Residence alterations, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Scottish Bank (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Scottish Bank: Agreement and fees, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Scottish Bank: Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Scottish Bank: Request for payments, 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Sedgefield Country Club: Proposed addition, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Servomation Caterers, Inc., 1969 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Simpson Office Building, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Southeast Elementary School, 1963-1967 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Stevens (Mr. and Mrs. A. F., Jr.) residence: Addition, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - United Securities Company, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - University of North Carolina at Greensboro: Shop and warehouse, 1968-1970 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - University of North Carolina at Greensboro: Specifications, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Wood (Mr. and Mrs. William A., Jr.) residence, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Office Records, 1948-1971; 1948 1971
  Office records contain correspondence, lists of prospective clients, personnel files, financial accounts, and promotional materials for Woodroof, Jr.’s firm.
  - Armfield (William, J., III), 1970 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Asheboro Urban Design, 1964-1967 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Blue Cross Insurance (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Book: The Architects' and Builders' Pocket-book by Frank Kidder (Box 29)
  - Company Reimbursements, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Contessa Moroni Imports, Inc., 1962 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Contractors: Qualifications, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Contributions, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 16, Folder 17)